Dennis Roberts fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Audio recordings, 1968 - 1982; F-160-2; 132 sound recordings; Physical description: series includes 134 audio cassettes and 4 audio tapes (reel-to-reel).
  - Webster / Svend Robinson; Jewett re: establishing Women's Committee, [ca 1975]; F-160-2-0-0-0-85 (Audio cassette OBJ-3437)
    A - Webster interviews Svend Robinson.
    B- Jewett re establishing Women's Committee.
    Webster, Jack; Svend Robinson; Jewett, Pauline; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-44.1 orig., F-160-item44.
  - SFU Pipes and Drums; AUCE strike; CBC interview union rep and Suart, 1975 - 1979; F-160-2-0-0-0-91 (Audio cassette OBJ-3443)
    A - SFU Pipes and Drums annual competition and awards night.
    B - AUCE Strike, union rep. Drina McCormack and SFU VP George Suart interviews on CBC.
    Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Drina McCormack; Suart, George; Association of University and College Employees, Local 2; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-56.1 orig., F-160-item56.
  - Jewett: Women's Rights; Ely Zwonkin, senior citizen SFU student, [ca 1975]; F-160-2-0-0-0-92 (Audio cassette OBJ-3444)
    A - Dr. Pauline Jewett, President - "Women's Rights.
    B - Ely Zwonkin, Senior citizen from the US who studied at SFU (see Comment Magazine article re his life in Russia).
    Jewett, Pauline; Ely Zwonkin; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-46.1 orig., F-160-item46.
  - Fotheringham / Jewett interview, [ca 1975]; F-160-2-0-0-0-93 (Audio cassette OBJ-3445)
    A - Dr. Pauline Jewett - interview by Alan Fotheringham
    Jewett, Pauline; Fotheringham, Alan; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-48.1 orig., F-160-item48.
  - SFU Pipes and Drums; Webster on PSA 7, Jewett, CAUT boycott, [ca 1975]; F-160-2-0-0-0-94 (Audio cassette OBJ-3446)
    A - The original SFU Pipes and Drums perform in SFU Theatre.
    B - Jack Webster spells out "new crisis" at SFU involving PSA 7, Pauline Jewett and CAUT boycott.
    Webster, Jack; Simon Fraser University Pipe Band; Canadian Association of University Teachers; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-55.1 orig., F-160-item55.
  - SFU Piper and Carson Graham School band; Prof. T.C. Byrne, 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-95 (Audio cassette OBJ-3447)
    A - SFU Piper Tom McMath plays the pipes as the Carson Graham School Band renders "Amazing Grace" in SFU theatre.
    B - Prof. T.C. Byrne (ACUIB) (he could have been chatting with university information officers from across Canada.)
    Tom McMath; Byrne, T.C.; Simon Fraser University Pipe Band; Carson Graham School; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-57.1 orig., F-160-item57.
  - SFU Pipers during Open House, 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-96 (Audio cassette OBJ-3448)
    A - SFU Pipers and "Massed Bands" parade on Mall during Open House (helped by the Triumph Street and others)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-58.1 orig., F-160-item58.
  - SFU Pipes and Drums, 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-97 (Audio cassette OBJ-3449)
    A, B - SFU Pipes and Drums; the students who kept a fine university tradition alive
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-60.1 orig., F-160-item60.
  - Yvonne Hamblin, Jewett statement on staying at SFU, 1976; F-160-2-0-0-0-102 (Audio cassette OBJ-3455)
    A - Yvonne Hamblin - Pianist.
    B- Jewett statement on staying at SFU.
    Yvonne Hamblin; Jewett, Pauline; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-42.1 orig., F-160-item42.
  - Roberts / Jewett interview, 1976; F-160-2-0-0-0-103 (Audio cassette OBJ-3456)
    A, B - Dr. Pauline Jewett after 2 years as President - interview with Dennis Roberts (note: starts after about 2 minutes)
    Jewett, Pauline; Roberts, Dennis; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-45.1 orig., F-160-item45.
  - Jewett / Truelove interview, Women's Athletic Coordinator, 9 January 1976; F-160-2-0-0-0-106 (Audio cassette OBJ-3459)
    A, B - Jewett / Rosemary? Truelove interview - Women's Athletic Coordinator
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-41.1 orig., F-160-item41.
  - Olympic Games music; CJOR Ted Sinnott interview, August 1976; F-160-2-0-0-0-107 (Audio cassette OBJ-3460, Audio cassette OBJ-3461)
    A - Olympic Games music.
    B - Ted Sinnott CJOR interview re rotten eggs SFU Pub blurb
    Sinnott, Ted; CJOR Radio; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-63.1 orig., F-160-item63.
  - Jim Felter, Art Gallery curator; Jewett on seeking nomination for NDP, 1977; F-160-2-0-0-0-108 (Audio cassette OBJ-3462)
    B - Jim Felter, Art Gallery curator - Interview re AQ garden pyramid; it's value as art, position and alignment, "it talks to me"
    A - cont'd // Jewett on Government amendment // statement on seeking nomination for NDP // News
    Felter, James W.; Jewett, Pauline; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-43.1 orig., F-160-item43.
  - Announcement re: Jewett resignation, Pedersen appointment; memorial service for Ed Larson, 1977; F-160-2-0-0-0-109 (Audio cassette OBJ-3463)
    A - Announcement re Presidency - Dr. Pauline Jewett resigning and Dr. George Pedersen being appointed.
    B - Memorial service for Ed Larson, PPandP.
    Jewett, Pauline; Pedersen, Knud George; Ed Larson; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-50.1 orig., F-160-item50.
  - SFU Pipers and Drums awards night, 1977; F-160-2-0-0-0-110 (Audio cassette OBJ-3464)
    A, B - SFU Pipers and Drums awards night
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-59.1 orig., F-160-item59.
  - Janet Brooks interview, 1977; F-160-2-0-0-0-111 (Audio cassette OBJ-3465)
    A, B - Interview with Janet Brooks, student, re solo trip to South America (Comment magazine)
    Janet Brooks; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-73.1 orig., F-160-item73.
  - Clifford Lloyd interview, 1977; F-160-2-0-0-0-112 (Audio cassette OBJ-3466)
    A, B - Clifford Lloyd interview
    Lloyd, Cliff; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-80.1 orig., F-160-item80.
  - Joachim Sandvoss; George Pedersen, 1978 - 1979; F-160-2-0-0-0-115 (Audio cassette OBJ-3469)
    A - Pedersen - continued; Dr. Joachim Sandvoss, Music Teacher, SFU (see Comment).
    B - Dr. George Pedersen - named new President of SFU
    Sandvoss, Joachim; Pedersen, Knud George; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-51.1 orig., F-160-item51.
  - Music by Prof. Joe Sandvoss, [1978?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-116 (Audio cassette OBJ-3470)
    A - Music arranged by Prof. Joe Sandvoss, Education (Comment)
    Sandvoss, Joachim; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-71.1 orig., F-160-item71.
  - Pedersen; Peter Hatch, glassblower, 1978 - 1980; F-160-2-0-0-0-117 (Audio cassette OBJ-3471)
    A - Dr. George Pedersen, President.
    B - Peter Hatch - Glassblower, Science Faculty (see Comment).
    Pedersen, Knud George; Peter Hatch; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-54.1 orig., F-160-item54.
  - Dr. George Pedersen - new SFU President first interview, 1978; F-160-2-0-0-0-118 (Audio cassette OBJ-3472)
    A, B - Dr. George Pedersen - new SFU President first interview (see Comment Magazine)
    Pedersen, Knud George; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-52.1 orig., F-160-item52.
  - John Sawatsky interview, 1978; F-160-2-0-0-0-119 (Audio cassette OBJ-3473, Audio cassette OBJ-3474)
    A, B - John Sawatsky interview
    John Sawatsky; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-74.1 orig., C-160-2-0-75.1 orig., F-160-item74, F-160-item75.
  - George Suart re: negotiations, 1978; F-160-2-0-0-0-120 (Audio cassette OBJ-3475)
    A - George Suart, VP Admin. re "Negotiations"
    Suart, George; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-81.1 orig., F-160-item81.
  - Memorial Service for 7 SFU students killed in air crash just before Christmas 1977 (Oregon), 12 January 1978; F-160-2-0-0-0-124 (Audio cassette OBJ-3479)
    A - Memorial Service for 7 SFU students killed in air crash just before Christmas 1977 (Oregon)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-68.1 orig., F-160-item68.
  - CJOR Reynolds / Pedersen interview; Webster / Suart / AUCE rep interview re: strike, 1979; F-160-2-0-0-0-125 (Audio cassette OBJ-3480)
    A - John Reynolds, CJOR, interviews new SFU President, Pedersen.
    B - cont'd; Later: Jack Webster interviews G. Suart and AUCE representative re Strike
    John Reynolds; Pedersen, Knud George; Webster, Jack; Suart, George; Association of University and College Employees, Local 2; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-53.1 orig., F-160-item53.
  - Gordon Shrum, 1980; F-160-2-0-0-0-126 (Audio cassette OBJ-3481)
    A, B - Dr. Gordon Shrum, SFU's 1st Chancellor who built SFU (see Comment Fall / Winter 1980)
    Shrum, Gordon; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-82.1 orig., F-160-item82.
  - Release the Hostages campaign; CBC interview with Lesley Ross, 1980; F-160-2-0-0-0-127 (Audio cassette OBJ-3482)
    A - One week into "Release the Hostages" campaign by UNS Staff - radio interview with Dennis Roberts.
    B - CBC interview with Lesley Ross (Bursar Don Ross' daughter), who wrote award-winning history of Richmond
    Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Leslie Ross; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-83.1 orig., F-160-item83.
  - Ted Sinnott memorial service, 1981; F-160-2-0-0-0-128 (Audio cassette OBJ-3483, Audio cassette OBJ-3484)
    A - Ted Sinnott's memorial service by the Three Flags.
    Sinnott, Ted; Sinnott, Ted; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-65.1 orig., F-160-item65.
  - Ray Parkinson, BoG Chair, 1981; F-160-2-0-0-0-129 (Audio cassette OBJ-3485)
    A, B - Dr. Ray Parkinson, psychologist (former MLA) who was BOG Chair
    Parkinson, Ray; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-79.1 orig., F-160-item79.
  - Terry Fox memorial service, 2 July 1981; F-160-2-0-0-0-130 (Audio cassette OBJ-3486, Optical disc: cd OBJ-3489)
    A - Terry Fox Memorial Service
    Fox, Terry; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-66.1 orig., F-160-item66.
  - Vern Bethel interview, 18 July 1981; F-160-2-0-0-0-131 (Audio cassette OBJ-3487)
    A, B - Interview with Vern Bethel, Charter student (Comment)
    Vern Bethel; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-77.1 orig., F-160-item77.
  - CKLG Alan Garr / Dennis Roberts interview, 12 September 1970; F-160-2-0-0-0-53 (Audio cassette OBJ-3404)
    A, B - Alan Garr, (CKLG) interviews Dennis Roberts
    CKLG Radio; Garr, Alan; Roberts, Dennis; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-78.1 orig., F-160-item78.
  - Tom Hammond, 1978; F-160-2-0-0-0-121
    A, B - Tom Hammond, Scottish born mature student who owned a pub in downtown Vancouver (Comment)
    Tom Hammond; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-84.1 orig., F-160-item84.
  - Doug Gyseman, 1978; F-160-2-0-0-0-122 (Audio cassette OBJ-3477)
    A, B - Doug Gyseman, audio specialist (then AV) (Comment)
    Gyseman, Doug; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-85.1 orig., F-160-item85.
  - Chris Hildred, 1977; F-160-2-0-0-0-113 (Audio cassette OBJ-3467)
    A, B - Chris Hildred, first-class photographer, AV (Comment)
    Hildred, Chris; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-86.1 orig., F-160-item86.
  - Jack Diamond interview, 1978; F-160-2-0-0-0-123 (Audio cassette OBJ-3478)
    A - Jack Diamond interview (with music of PDQ Bach, "Tom Jones" (see Comment Spring)
    Diamond, Jack; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-87.1 orig., F-160-item87.
  - "The Happy Hooker" (Xaviera Hollander), 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-98 (Audio cassette OBJ-3450)
    A, B - "the Happy Hooker" (Xaviera Hollander) re book.
    Hollander, Xaviera; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-88.1 orig., F-160-item88.
  - Webster / McGeer interview; Carallyn Bowes, 1976; F-160-2-0-0-0-104 (Audio cassette OBJ-3457)
    A - Jack Webster interview with Dr. Pat McGeer.
    B - Carallyn Bowes - ran across Canada to join Kinesiology progr.
    Webster, Jack; McGeer, Pat; Bowes, Carallyn; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-89.1 orig., F-160-item89.
  - CKNW Art Finley program: Carallyn Bowes; Captain Cook lectures, 1976; F-160-2-0-0-0-105 (Audio cassette OBJ-3458)
    A - Carallyn Bowes - on Art Finley (CKNW) program // Poly Party Strike.
    B - Carallyn Bowes - interview en route / arrival in Vancouver (Comment) // Captain Cook lectures
    Bowes, Carallyn; Finley, Art; CKNW Radio; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-90.1 orig., F-160-item90.
  - Mariela Johansen and Jeanne Henry, Physics students, 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-84 (Audio cassette OBJ-3436)
    A - Interview with Physics students Mariela Johansen and Jeanne Henry re upcoming Physics Undergrad Conference, (Comment)
    Mariela Johansen; Jeanne Henry; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-91.1 orig., F-160-item91.
  - University Information Officers re: "Campus Unrest" at PR Society, Vancouver, 1971; F-160-2-0-0-0-55 (Audio cassette OBJ-3406)
    A, B - University Information Officers (Roberts, SFU and Arnie Myers, UBC) re "Campus Unrest" at PR Society, Vancouver
    Roberts, Dennis; Myers, Arnie; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-92.1 orig., F-160-item92.
  - Dr. Calvert, proposed Engineering program, 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-99 (Audio cassette OBJ-3451)
    A - Interviewee not identified.
    B - Dr. Calvert discusses proposed Engineering program.
    Calvert, Thomas W.; School of Engineering Science; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-93.1 orig., F-160-item93.
  - Dr. Fattah re: Criminology department, 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-86 (Audio cassette OBJ-3438)
    A - Dr. Fattah statement about establishing Criminology Dept.
    Fattah, Ezzat A.; School of Criminology; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-94.1 orig., F-160-item94.
  - Convocation; student publicity blurb, 24 May 1969; F-160-2-0-0-0-21 (Audio cassette OBJ-3374)
    A - Convocation - Bagpipes, Honorary Degrees, convocation address by Robert McKenzie.
    B - SFU publicity blurb to accompany information pamphlet.
    McKenzie, Robert; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-95.1 orig., F-160-item95.
  - John Kenward, first student elected to SFU BoG; holography, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-33 (Audio cassette OBJ-3385)
    A - John Kenward, first student elected to SFU BOG.
    B - Uses of holography.
    John Kenward; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-96.1 orig., F-160-item96.
  - Tony Buzan, first SFU Student Council President, [ca 1976]; F-160-2-0-0-0-100 (Audio cassette OBJ-3452)
    A, B - Interview with Tony Buzan, 1st President, SFU Student Council makes name for himself in UK (see Comment)
    Buzan, Tony; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-97.1 orig., F-160-item97.
  - Rick Hyde / Ted Wells interview, 1977; F-160-2-0-0-0-114 (Audio cassette OBJ-3468)
    A, B - Prof. Ted Wells, Chemistry Dept. interview by Rick Hyde (see Comment Spring)
    Wells, Edward J.; Rick Hyde; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-98.1 orig., F-160-item98.
  - Future of universities; Prof. Phyllis Auty interview, 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-87 (Audio cassette OBJ-3439)
    A - Future of Universities - speeches and discussion.
    B - cont'd // Interview with Prof. Phyllis Auty.
    Auty, Phyllis; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-99.1 orig., F-160-item99.
  - Trenna Jean Hunter interview, President of Staff Association, 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-70 (Audio cassette OBJ-3420)
    A, B - Interview with Trenna Jean Hunter, cashier supervisor and President of Staff Association (see Comment)
    Hunter, Trenna; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-100.1 orig., F-160-item100.
  - Gary Rush PSA interview; Joel Smith interview, 1971; F-160-2-0-0-0-56 (Audio cassette OBJ-3407)
    A - Prof. Gary Rush, PSA interview.
    B - Joel Smith, artist, SFU Communications Centre interview (see Comment).
    Rush, Gary; Smith, Joel; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-101.1 orig., F-160-item101.
  - Admissions Committee, student discussion, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-34 (Audio cassette OBJ-3386)
    A - 3rd part Admissions Committee / Student Discussion / Trailers Discussion [Disturbance: "We want a revolution and we want it now"!].
    B - Draft of speech on Education by Dr. John Ellis?
    Ellis, John F.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-102.1 orig., F-160-item102.
  - Dan Birch interview, 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-88 (Audio cassette OBJ-3440)
    A, B - Interview with Prof. Dan Birch (see Comment)
    Birch, Daniel R.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-103.1 orig., F-160-item103.
  - George Suart interview; Webster / Stevens re: fishermen's strike, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-35 (Audio cassette OBJ-3387)
    A - Interview with George Suart, VP Admin. re personal history and professional life (see Comment).
    B - Jack Webster / Stevens - Fishermen's strike.
    Suart, George; Webster, Jack; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-104.1 orig., F-160-item104.
  - Ted Sterling (Computing Science) interview, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-36 (Audio cassette OBJ-3388)
    A, B - Dr. Ted Sterling, Chair of Computing Science interview (see Comment)
    Sterling, Ted; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-105.1 orig., F-160-item105.
  - Mary Trainer and Rick Antonson, publishers, 1972; F-160-2-0-0-0-60 (Audio cassette OBJ-3411)
    A, B - Mary Trainer and Rick Antonson - young publishers of B.C. history books (see Comment)
    Mary Trainer; Rick Antonson; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-106.1 orig., F-160-item106.
  - Sandra Wilking, SFU International Office, [197-]; F-160-2-0-0-0-49 (Audio cassette OBJ-3401)
    A - Sandra Wilking, SFU International Office and SFU student re "The World Becomes A Classroom" (see Comment).
    B - [originally listed as SPEC interview, however Roberts believes it is Dr. Bert Turnbull, Biological Sciences].
    Sandra Wilking; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-107.1 orig., F-160-item107.
  - Gordon Hardy; Gordon Paulsen, November 1970; F-160-2-0-0-0-54 (Audio cassette OBJ-3405)
    A - Gordon Hardy, one-time editor and writer for The Peak (see Comment).
    B - Gordon Paulsen, C.A., Bursar's Office, re MBA program.
    Hardy, Gordon; Gordon Paulsen; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-108.1 orig., F-160-item108.
  - Mennell / Newton (Modern Languages) interview; Mennell / Somjee interview, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-37 (Audio cassette OBJ-3389)
    A - Prof. Newton, Modern Languages, interviewed by K. Mennell.
    B - Prof. Somjee, PSA, interview by K. Mennell.
    Mennell, Ken; Newton, Brian E.; Somjee, A.H.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-109.1 orig., F-160-item109.
  - Mel Woolley, Naheeno Park, 1973; F-160-2-0-0-0-66 (Audio cassette OBJ-3416)
    A, B - Mel Woolley, Entrepreneurial Student, created Naheeno Park and "make-work" projects (see Comment).
    Mel Woolley; Naheeno Park; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-110.1 orig., F-160-item110.
  - CKNW news, Prof. Tony Arrott, 1975; F-160-2-0-0-0-89 (Audio cassette OBJ-3441)
    A, B - CKNW news - Prof. Tony Arrott discusses liquid cyrstals and his life (see Comment)
    CKNW Radio; Arrott, Anthony S.; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-111.1 orig., F-160-item111.
  - Dr. Ed Lipinski (Health Service); Prof. Gygax (Physics), [197-]; F-160-2-0-0-0-48 (Audio cassette OBJ-3400)
    A - Dr. Ed Lipinski, SFU Psychiatrist and Director of Health Serv. (His death in a motoring accident in Spain shocked the Campus Community).
    B - Prof. Gygax, Physicist in magnetic fields.
    Lipinski, Edward; Suso Gygax; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-112.1 orig., F-160-item112.
  - Prof. Larry Boland (Economics and Commerce), 1974; F-160-2-0-0-0-71 (Audio cassette OBJ-3421)
    A, B. -Prof. Larry Boland, Economics and Commerce, and a member of Senate
    Boland, Larry; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-113.1 orig., F-160-item113.
  - Dr. Vergin (Economic and Commerce); Ted Sinnott; Rev. Duncan Chalmers, [1976?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-101 (Audio cassette OBJ-3453, Audio cassette OBJ-3454)
    A - Dr. Vergin, Economics and Commerce (interviewed by Rick Hyde re his work with Marlon Brando and his study of gambling) (see Comment) // Ted Sinnott radio interview.
    B - Sinnott cont'd // Computing Centre // Rev. Duncan Chalmers.
    Vergin, Roger; Rick Hyde; Sinnott, Ted; Duncan Chalmers; Marlon Brando; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-114.1 orig., F-160-item114.
  - Dr. John Ellis, Education, makes short statement on transfer credit, [1968?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3358)
    A - Dr. John Ellis, Education, makes short statement on transfer credit
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-115.1 orig., F-160-item115.
  - Jack Webster and Gullen, Vancouver School Board, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-38 (Audio cassette OBJ-3390)
    A - Jack Webster and Gullen, Vancouver School Board re competence in English
    Webster, Jack; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-116.1 orig., F-160-item116.
  - Dr. John Ellis (Education), speech; Webster interview, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-39 (Audio cassette OBJ-3391)
    A - Dr. John Ellis, Education, speech to Rotary Club "Conspiracy of Status" // Webster Interview.
    B - Webster Interview cont'd
    Ellis, John F.; Webster, Jack; Rotary Club of Vancouver; Sound recordings
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-160-2-0-117.1 orig., F-160-item117.
  - Jack Webster interviews: Dr. Clark (Academic Planning, UBC), David Anderson and Allan Williams, [197-?]; F-160-2-0-0-0-40 (Audio cassette OBJ-3392)
    A - Webster / Dr. Clark, Academic Planning, UBC.